(Leonard:)Boy, that's a toughie.
(Penny:)You still see her?
(Leonard:)Well, no, not socially.
(Leonard:)But, you know,
just at work.
You work with her?!
(groans)
How could you not tell me that?!
(Leonard:)I wanted to tell you in the car,
but you told me to stop talking!
(Penny:)Oh, okay. So you're saying
this is my fault?
(Sheldon:)No, of course not.
(stammers) Okay, l-look,
(Leonard:)instead of fighting,
(Leonard:)why don't we dim the lights,
(Leonard:)um, get naked and make a baby?
(Leonard:)I was trying
to lighten the mood.
(Leonard:)It's not easy. You try it.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Hello, Mother.
(Mrs Cooper:)Shelly! How's my baby doing?
(Sheldon:)I just wanted to let you know
(Sheldon:)that you can remove Amy
from your nightly prayers.
(Sheldon:)Unless you're open
to praying for
(Sheldon:)a beehive to fall on her head.
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh, what's going on?
(Sheldon:)She broke up with me.
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh, Shelly.
(Sheldon:)No, I'll be okay.
(Sheldon:)But I think that I'd like